{
    "id": "2dddef96a2da4faab9d95d936e4d0a31",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His liver cancer was ........................ by years of drinking.",
            "description": "To bring on is to cause something negative to happen. ",
            "answers": [
                "brought up",
                "brought out",
                "brought on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................... my grandparents yesterday.",
            "description": "To call on someone is to visit them. ",
            "answers": [
                "called in",
                "called on",
                "called for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Even though the team had little chance of winning, their fans cheered them .................. throughout the match.",
            "description": "To cheer somebody on is to support them by giving words of encouragement. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am having a bad day. I really need someone to cheer me ..................",
            "description": "To cheer somebody up is to try to make them happier.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju has .......................... with a brilliant idea for a TV show.",
            "description": "To come up with an idea is to introduce it. ",
            "answers": [
                "come up",
                "come out",
                "come off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was going to leave on Monday but something ..................... and I had to cancel the trip.",
            "description": "Come up can be used to talk about an unexpected occurrence. ",
            "answers": [
                "came over",
                "came up",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "'......................', said the teacher to the visitor.",
            "description": "Come in = enter",
            "answers": [
                "Come in",
                "Come up",
                "Come off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............... some old photos while cleaning the cupboard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came across",
                "came over",
                "came at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were discussing some private matters when mother ........................",
            "description": "To cut in is to interrupt someone while they were talking. ",
            "answers": [
                "cut out",
                "cut up",
                "cut in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Grandmother always ............................ to bring us little gifts.",
            "description": "To drop in or drop by is to stop by for a visit.",
            "answers": [
                "drops in",
                "drops by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When I am late, my brother drops me ................... at work.",
            "description": "To drop somebody off is to leave them in their destination. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They made a sincere effort to save their marriage but in the end it ......................",
            "description": "When a marriage falls apart, it fails. ",
            "answers": [
                "fell down",
                "fell apart",
                "fell off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}